html_questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What is the biggest naturally aspirated engine the Aston Martin sell?:',
        'answers': ['V8', 'v12', '1.8'],
        'correct': 'V12'
    },
    {
        'question': '''You may remember in James bond there is a "special" branch
         for customiseable anything:''',
        'answers': ['Cue', 'Q', 'K'],
        'correct': 'Q'
    },
    {
        'question': '''The most iconic Aston Martin is:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage', 'DB9', 'DB5'],
        'correct': 'DB5'
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins show stopper for safety:''',
        'answers': ['There are extra airbags in the seats', 
        'The bonnet air bags to cover the screen for reinforcement',
        '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom pushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''],
        'correct': '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom oushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''In the vanquish there is a option to have a square steering
        wheel:''',
        'answers': ['True',
        '''False'''],
        'correct': '''True'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins new SUV:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'DBX'],
        'correct': '''DBX'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What Is the smallest car aston martin have ever made:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'Cygnet'],
        'correct': '''Cygent'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''There is currently 2 new engines which are AMG based what are these:''',
        'answers': ['V6 twin turbo',
        'V8 twin turbo',
        'V12 twin turbo'],
        'correct': '''V12 twin turbo'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''The DBS Superleggera has a 0.60 time of .... and has .... bhp:''',
        'answers': ['3.4 715',
        '4.4 550',
        '3.8 650'],
        'correct': '''3.4 715'''
    },

    html_questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What is the biggest naturally aspirated engine the Aston Martin sell?:',
        'answers': ['V8', 'v12', '1.8'],
        'correct': 'V12'
    },
    {
        'question': '''You may remember in James bond there is a "special" branch
         for customiseable anything:''',
        'answers': ['Cue', 'Q', 'K'],
        'correct': 'Q'
    },
    {
        'question': '''The most iconic Aston Martin is:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage', 'DB9', 'DB5'],
        'correct': 'DB5'
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins show stopper for safety:''',
        'answers': ['There are extra airbags in the seats', 
        'The bonnet air bags to cover the screen for reinforcement',
        '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom pushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''],
        'correct': '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom oushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''In the vanquish there is a option to have a square steering
        wheel:''',
        'answers': ['True',
        '''False'''],
        'correct': '''True'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins new SUV:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'DBX'],
        'correct': '''DBX'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What Is the smallest car aston martin have ever made:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'Cygnet'],
        'correct': '''Cygent'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''There is currently 2 new engines which are AMG based what are these:''',
        'answers': ['V6 twin turbo',
        'V8 twin turbo',
        'V12 twin turbo'],
        'correct': '''V12 twin turbo'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''The DBS Superleggera has a 0.60 time of .... and has .... bhp:''',
        'answers': ['3.4 715',
        '4.4 550',
        '3.8 650'],
        'correct': '''3.4 715'''
    },

    ##

    html_questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What is the biggest naturally aspirated engine the Aston Martin sell?:',
        'answers': ['V8', 'v12', '1.8'],
        'correct': 'V12'
    },
    {
        'question': '''You may remember in James bond there is a "special" branch
         for customiseable anything:''',
        'answers': ['Cue', 'Q', 'K'],
        'correct': 'Q'
    },
    {
        'question': '''The most iconic Aston Martin is:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage', 'DB9', 'DB5'],
        'correct': 'DB5'
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins show stopper for safety:''',
        'answers': ['There are extra airbags in the seats', 
        'The bonnet air bags to cover the screen for reinforcement',
        '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom pushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''],
        'correct': '''The last and most extreme of 70mph crumple zone will drop the engine
        V8 OR V12 out the bottom oushing the car up and over engine to
        decrease imapact to cockpit'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''In the vanquish there is a option to have a square steering
        wheel:''',
        'answers': ['True',
        '''False'''],
        'correct': '''True'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What is Aston Martins new SUV:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'DBX'],
        'correct': '''DBX'''
    },
    {
        'question': '''What Is the smallest car aston martin have ever made:''',
        'answers': ['Vantage',
        'DB11',
        'Cygnet'],
        'correct': '''Cygent'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''There is currently 2 new engines which are AMG based what are these:''',
        'answers': ['V6 twin turbo',
        'V8 twin turbo',
        'V12 twin turbo'],
        'correct': '''V12 twin turbo'''
    },
    {    
        'question': '''The DBS Superleggera has a 0.60 time of .... and has .... bhp:''',
        'answers': ['3.4 715',
        '4.4 550',
        '3.8 650'],
        'correct': '''3.4 715'''
    },